BRIAN OCHIENG' OMBEE



Contact

Address:

P.O Box 7-00200, Kikuyu

Phone:

0710 454 213

Email:

brianombee@gmail.com

Languages

Luo Kiswahili English

Programming Languages:

JavaScript, HTML5 AutoCAD, PROKON. Robot

Summary

I write with enthusiasm in response to your offer for Civil Engineering position. Your institution's stellar reputation for providing quality services and project support to your clients is well-known, and I am motivated to join your team. As an undergraduate, I have balanced my heavy course load and several extracurricular activities which have allowed me to enhance skills that would be relevant to this role, example, 3D design and modelling, an understanding of material engineering and experience with different manufacturing technologies.

Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused

Experience

Assistant Engineer ZJCC 10/22 – 12/22

Intern Assistant Engineer Nairobi Expressway Project Phase 2 – 10/2021 – 5/2022

Attachee - 09/2021 to 12/2021

Nairobi City County, Nairobi Metropolitan Services

- Engineering drawing and detailing
- Bill of Quantities
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.

Site Manager – 05/2021 to 08/2021

Lorac Ventures, Siaya

• Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.

Education

Bachelor of Science: Civil and Construction Engineering, University of Nairobi, 2022.

Alliance High School – Grade A Plain, 2015.

Referees

Eng. Allan Engoke, Kenya Pipeline Company

0722 890 828

Eng. Hesbon Okari, University of Nairobi

0723 728 149





DG002089

UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI

This is to certify that

DG002089822011409F16/1752/2017Brian Ombee OchlengB4 CHEL 71
DG002089822011409F16/1752/2017Brian Ombee OchlengB4 CHEL 71
DG002089822011409F16/1752/2017Brian Ombee OchlengB4 CHEL 71
DG002089822011409F16/1752/2017Brian OmBrian Ombee OchlengB6 CHEL 71
DG002089822011409F16/1752/2017Brian OmBrian Ombee OchlengB7
DG002089822011409F16/1752/2017Brian Ombee OchlengB7
DG00208982011409F16/1752/2017Brian Ombee OchlengB7
DG00208902011409F16/1752/2017Brian Ombee OchlengB7
DG00208902011409F16/1409F16/1752/2017Brian Ombee OchlengB7
DG00208902011409F16/1752/20

having satisfied the requirements for the award of the degree of the

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN CIVIL ENGINEERING

Second Class Honours (Lower Division)

was admitted to the degree at a Congregation held at this University on the

Twenty Third Day of September in the Year 2022

VICE-CHANCELLOR



J. Qgengo

DEPUTY VICE-CHANCELLOR (ACADEMIC AFFAIRS)

F16/1752/2017